A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Mexico, RG 6, SG 13 FA398
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Office Files, 1943-1965; 1
  - Ford Foundation - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - France - 1959-1962 Freeman, Wayne H. - 1961 Frolick, E.F. - 1959-1960, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Galarraga, Jose Rafael (Point IV Fellow-Ecuador), 1953-1958 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - General Correspondence (A-Z), 1949-1958 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - General Correspondence - Africa and Asia, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - General Correspondence - Caribbean, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 230)
  - General Correspondence - Central America, 1947-1960 (Box 21, Folder 231)
  - General Correspondence - Europe, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 232)
  - General Correspondence - Mexico, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 233)
  - General Correspondence - Mexico, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 234)
  - General Correspondence - Mexico - Government Agencies, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 235)
  - General Correspondence - Mexico - RF Staff, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 236)
  - General Correspondence - Mexico - Unofficial, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 237)
  - General Correspondence - North America (A-M), 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 238)
  - General Correspondence - North America (N-Z), 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 239)
  - General Correspondence - Smith, Donald L., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 240)
  - General Correspondence - South America, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 241)
  - General Correspondence - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - Geneticists Meeting I - (Sept. 26-Oct. 8, 1949 -- Mexico) - General Files (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - (March 31-April 12, 1952 -- Brazil) - Delegates Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - (March 31-April 12, 1952 -- Brazil) - Delegates Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 245)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - General Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 246)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - Invitation List, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 247)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - Program, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 248)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - Telegrams, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 249)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - Titles Received, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 250)
  - Geneticists Meeting II - Travel, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 251)
  - Geneticists Meeting III (June 20-July 1, 1955 -- Colombia) - Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 23, Folder 252)
  - Geneticists Meeting III - Program, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 253)
  - Genetics (W.M. Myers) - (n.d) Genetics Society of America - 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 254)
  - Georgia - 1962 Germ Plasm Conference - 1959 Germany - 1960-1962, 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 255)
  - Ghana - 1962 Gibler, John W. (Diary) - 1962 Gillham, Fred E.M. - 1962 Goppinger, Walter W. - 1962 (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - Gomez, Marte R. - (Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1944-1947 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Gonzalez Gallardo, Alfonso - (Sub-Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Gonzalez Gallardo, Alfonso - (Sub-Secretario de Agricultura y Fomento-Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - Governmental Correspondence (Mexico), 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Great Britain - 1962 Green, V.E. (University of Florida) - 1962 Gregory, Walton C. (North Carolina State U.) - 1962 Grobman, Alexander (Harvard University) - 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Guanajauto, State of, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 262)
  - Guatemala - Arevalo, Boris, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 263)
  - Guatemala - Ensayo Observaciones de Colecciones, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Guatemala - Ensayo Observaciones de Colecciones, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Guatemala - Ensayo Uniformes de Rendimiento, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 269)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 272)
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 273)
  - Guatemala - Instituto Agropeacuario Nacional, 1947-1956 (Box 25, Folder 274)
  - Guatemala - Libros de Campo, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 275)
  - Guatemala - Reports, 1956-1962 (Box 25, Folder 276)
  - Guerrero, State of - 1952-1961 Guevara, Jose (I.N.I.A.) - 1962 Guinea - 1962 Gutierrez, Mario - 1961, 1952-1962 (Box 25, Folder 277)
  - Haag, Herman M - 1962 Haiti - 1959-1962 Hanson, Warren D. - 1961-1962 Hampstead, Dale - 1961 (Box 25, Folder 278)
  - Harrar, J.G. (George) - Correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box 25, Folder 279)
  - Harrar, J.G. (George) Diaries - 1943-1952 Five Year Report - 1943-1948 (Box 25, Folder 280)
  - Hartwig, Norman - 1961 Harvey, Paul H. - 1958-1961 Hatheway, William H. - 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - Hawaii - 1962 Hayes, Guy S. - 1952-1956 Herbicides - 1958-1960, 1952-1962 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Hernandez, Efraim, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 283)
  - Hidalgo, State of - 1950-1961 Hoffmann-Pinther and Bosworth S.A. - 1953-1956 Holland - 1960-1962, 1950-1962 (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Honduras - Ensayo de Uniforme de Rendimiento, 1956, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 285)
  - Honduras - Escuela Agricola Panamericana, 1943-1956 (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 287)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 288)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 289)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 26, Folder 290)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 291)
  - Honduras - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 292)
  - Horticulture Correspondence - 1958-1959 Reports - 1956-1960 (Box 26, Folder 293)
  - Hu, Wilma Wie-Lin - 1966 Hungary - 1962 Huss, Donald - 1962, 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Idaho - 1962 Illinois - 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Immigration Matters, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - India - 1952 Indian Agricultural Program - 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 297)
  - Indiana University - 1959 Indonesia - 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 298)
  - Instituto de Investigaciones Agricolo (SAG), 1947-1958 (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Instituto de Nutricion de Centro America y Panama, 1949-1957 (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales, 1959-1961 (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Agricolas (INIA) Animal Nutrition - 1961-1962 Budgets - 1962 Construction Project INIA Headquarters - 1962 (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - INIA Department of Agricultural Economy - 1961-1962 Department of Beans and Soybeans - 1961-1962 Department of Cereals - 1961-1962 Department of Entomology - 1961 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - INIA Department of Forages - 1961-1962 Department of Herbicides - 1961 Department of Horticulture - 1961-1962 Department of Oil Plants - 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - INIA Department of Plant Pathology - 1961-1962 Department of Technical Promotion - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - INIA - Department of Zootechnia, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - INIA Director General - 1961-1962 General Correspondence - 1961-1962 Maize and Sorghum Section - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 308)
  - INIA - Personnel - Curriculum Vitae, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - INIA - Personnel - General, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - INIA - Personnel - Projected Needs for Trained Personnel, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - INIA Presidential Decree - 1960 Project Committee - 1962 Publications Committee - 1962, 1960-1962 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - INIA - Reorganization of Research Activities, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - INIA - Reorganization of Research Activities, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - INIA - Rules and Procedures, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - INIA - Seed Laboratory, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - INIA Subdirector Jose Guevara Calderon - 1961-1962 Subdirector N. Sanchez Duron - 1961-1962 Subdirector Jose Luis Spota - 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - INIA - Workshops, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Instituto Nacional de Investigacion Pecuaria, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Instituto Nacional de Nutriologia, 1948-1954 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Instituto Nacional de Nutriologia - Statistics, 1948-1951 (Box 29, Folder 321)
  - Instituto para el Mejoramiento de la Produccion de Azucar - 1958-1960 Instituto Politechnio Nacional - 1947 Instituto Technologico Azucarera Veracruzano - 1960, 1947-1960 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Campo Apodaca, 1954-1956 (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Leonel Robles (Correspondence), 1948-1959 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - Leonel Robles (Correspondence), 1948-1959 (Box 29, Folder 328)
  - Instituto Technologico y de Estudios Superiores Monterrey - School of Agronomy, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 329)
  - Insurance, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Inter-American Congress of Farmers and Agronomists, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Inter-American Corn Crop Improvement Program, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Inter-American Food Crop Improvement Program, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Inter-American Maize Improvement Program, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Inter-American Research Symposium (Role of Communications in Agricultural Development), October 5-13, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Inter-American Society for Plant and Soil Scientists - 4th Annual Meeting (Chile), November 25-December 1, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 336)
  - Inter-American Society for Plant and Soil Scientists - 5th Annual Meeting (Argentina), November 5-18, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - Inter-American Wheat Improvement Program, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 338)
  - International Conference of Agricultural Economists - 1961 International Corn Breeding Program - 1961 International Cultural Center, A.C. - 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 339)
  - International Rice Research Institute - 1963-1965 International Wheat Improvement Program - 1959-1960, 1959-1965 (Box 30, Folder 340)
  - International Wheat Rust Conference, March 18-24, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 341)
  - Iowa - 1958-1962 Iowa State College/University - 1953-1954, 1959-1961, 1953-1962 (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Iraq - 1962 Israel - 1962 Italy - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - Jalisco, State of, 1953-1962 (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Jamaica - 1957-1962 Japan - 1962 (Box 31, Folder 345)
  - Jenkins, Merle T. - 1961 Jimenez, Jose - 1959 Jimenez, Mario Gutierrez - 1961-1962, 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 346)
  - Johnson, E.C. - 1961-1962 Johnston, John - 1962 Jordan - 1962 (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Kansas - 1958-1959 Kellogg Foundation Fellows-General - 1947-1949 Kellogg Foundation Fellows-Romero Lainez, Roberto - 1947-1949, 1962, 1947-1962 (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Kentucky - 1962 Kenya - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Latin-American Soils Scientists Meeting - October 19-24, 1953 Leng, Earl R. - 1961 Liberia - 1961, 1953-1961 (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - Livestock Improvement Project - 1953 Longley, Albert E. - 1959-1962 (Box 31, Folder 351)
  - Lonnquist, John H. - 1959-1962 Louisiana - 1962 Louisiana State University Library - 1960 (Box 31, Folder 352)
  - McClintock, Barbara - 1959-1962 McKelvey, John J. - 1945-1951, 1945-1962 (Box 32, Folder 353)
  - McNeish, Richard S. - 1960-1962 Madagascar - 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 354)
  - Maize Committee (Minutes) - 1959 Maize Reports - 1959 Mazie Seed Shipments - 1962, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 355)
  - Malca, Isaac - 1962 Mali, Republic of - 1962 Mangelsdorf, Paul C. - 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 356)
  - MAP (Mexican Agricultural Program) - Abstracts, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 357)
  - MAP - Activity Reports, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 360)
  - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports, 1945-1951 (Box 32, Folder 361)
  - MAP - Advisory Committee and Trustee Reports - Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - MAP - Applicants-Staff Positions, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - MAP - Budget, 1957, 1962, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 364)
  - MAP - Diaries, 1944-1962 (Box 33, Folder 365)
  - MAP - Diaries and Memoranda, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 366)
  - MAP Entertainment - 1960-1962 Federal Subsidy - 1955-1958, 1955-1960 (Box 33, Folder 367)
  - MAP - Fellows-Non RF, 1953-1958 (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - MAP - Film Project - "Mexican Agricultural Program", 1950 (Box 33, Folder 369)
  - MAP - Form Letters, 1953-1962 (Box 33, Folder 370)
  - MAP - Friends and Collaborators, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 371)
  - MAP Grants-Scholarships - 1943-1963 Grants-Travel - 1963-1966, 1943-1966 (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - MAP - Invitations, 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 373)
  - MAP - Itineraries, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - MAP Library - 1959-1962 Living Accomodations - 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 376)
  - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 377)
  - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - MAP - Memoranda, 1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1957-1962 (Box 34, Folder 379)
  - MAP - Orders-Supplies, Equipment, Seeds, 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 380)
  - MAP - Reports, 1950-1962 (Box 34, Folder 381)
  - MAP - Reports, 1950-1962 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - MAP - Six Year Review (J.G. Harrar), 1943-1949 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - MAP - Staff - Directory and Organization, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - MAP - Staff - Long Distance Telephone Calls, 1960-1962 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - MAP - Staff - Meetings, 1950-1958 (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - MAP - Staff - Personnel, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 387)
  - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 388)
  - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 389)
  - MAP - Visitors, 1960-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 390)
  - MAP - Workshops, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 391)
  - Maradiaga, Jorge A. - 1965-1966 Marin Diaz, Francisco (Kellogg Foundation Fellow) - 1947-1949, 1947-1966 (Box 35, Folder 392)
  - Maryland - 1959-1962 Massachusetts - 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 393)
  - Mennonite Central Committee Trainee - 1954-1958 Mercator Agricola, S.A. - 1959 Meteorology - 1959, 1954-1959 (Box 35, Folder 394)
  - Mexican-United States Agricultural Commission, 1944-1946 (Box 35, Folder 395)
  - Mexican-United States Agricultural Commission, 1944-1946 (Box 35, Folder 396)
  - Mexico (State of) Financial Matters, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 397)
  - Mexico (State of) Official and General Correspondence, 1946-1959 (Box 35, Folder 398)
  - Mexico (State of) Official and General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 399)
  - Mexico (State of) RF-SAG Program, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 400)
  - Mexico (United Mexican States-UMS) Agricultural Personnel - 1961-1962 Convenio (RF-Mexican Government) - 1954, 1954-1962 (Box 36, Folder 401)
  - Mexico (United Mexican States-UMS) Corn - 1961 Cotton (I.N.I.A.) - 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 402)
  - Mexico (United Mexican States-UMS) Delegacion Administrativa (SAG) - 1953-1955 Direccion General de Defensa Agricola (SAG) - 1949-1960 (Box 36, Folder 403)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Entomology (I.N.I.A.), 1961 (Box 36, Folder 404)
  - Mexico (UMS) Federal Agencies - 1952 Federal Subsidy - 1947-1953 (Box 36, Folder 405)
  - Mexico (UMS) Forage Utilization (I.N.I.A.) - 1961 General Correspondence - 1954-1962 (Box 36, Folder 406)
  - Mexico (UMS) Horticulture - 1961 Interamerican Wheat Improvement Program - 1961 (Box 36, Folder 407)
  - Mexico (UMS) Maderera del Tropico - 1952 Meat Production - 1961, 1952-1961 (Box 36, Folder 408)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Meetings-Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 409)
  - Mexico - Milling and Baking Laboratory (National School of Agriculture-Chapingo), 1955-1958 (Box 36, Folder 410)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Minister of Agriculture (Nazario S. Ortiz Garza), 1946-1952 (Box 37, Folder 411)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Minister of Agriculture (Nazario S. Ortiz Garza), 1946-1952 (Box 37, Folder 412)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Minister of Agriculture (Nazario S. Ortiz Garza), 1946-1952 (Box 37, Folder 413)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Minister of Agriculture (Gilberto Flores Munoz), 1953-1958 (Box 37, Folder 414)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Minister of Agriculture (Julian Rodriguez Adame), 1958-1960 (Box 37, Folder 415)
  - Mexico (UMS) Newspapers and Magazines - 1961 Nutrition - 1961 (Box 37, Folder 416)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Poultry (I.N.I.A.-RF), 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 417)
  - Mexico (UMS) - President of the Republic (Miguel A. Valdes and Adolfo L. Mateos), 1947-1952, 1957-1960 (Box 37, Folder 418)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Productura Nacional de Semillas, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 419)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Report - Comite Bancario Organizador de Uniones de Credito Agricola, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 420)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Report - Flora, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 421)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Report - La Investigacion Agricola en Mexico, 1854-1954 (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - Mexico (UMS) Report - Land Distribution - 1960 Library - 1961-1962, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 423)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Report - M.A.P., 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Report - Miscellaneous, 1944-1960 (Box 37, Folder 425)
  - Mexico (UMS) Reunion de Directores o Jefes (SAG) - 1960 Rice Program - 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 426)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Seed Certification, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 427)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Seed Requests and Technical Assistance, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 428)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Seed Requests and Technical Assistance, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Mexico (UMS) Sorghum - 1961 Speeches and Reports - 1959-1961 (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Sugar Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Sugar Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - Mexico (UMS) Vegetable Crops - 1955 Weed Control - 1961, 1955-1961 (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - Mexico (UMS) - Wheat, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - Mexico City College, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - Mexletter, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 436)
  - Mexletter, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 437)
  - Michigan, University of (Centrop) - 1959 Michoacan, State of - 1954-1960 Minnesota - 1959-1962, 1954-1962 (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Mexico, 1953-1962 (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - United States-Alphabetical, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - United States-Alphabetical, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - United States-Alphabetical, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - United States-Chronological, 1958-1962 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - Miscellaneous Meetings - Central and South America - 1948-1956 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - Miscellaneous Meetings - Mexico, 1952-1956 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1945-1960 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Mississippi - 1962 Missouri - 1960 Missouri Botanical Garden - 1959, 1959-1962 (Box 40, Folder 447)
  - Morelos, State of - 1952-1956 Morfologia Comparativa de Los Hongos - 1944 Myren, Delbert T. - 1962, 1944-1962 (Box 40, Folder 448)
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.A.) - 1959-1961 National School of Agriculture (Chapingo) - 1960-1962, 1959-1962 (Box 40, Folder 449)
  - Nayarit, State of - 1956-1961 Neal, N.P. - 1961-1962 Nebraska - 1961 (Box 40, Folder 450)
  - Nelson, Oliver E. - 1958-1962 Netherlands - 1960 New Caledonia - 1962 (Box 40, Folder 451)
  - New Jersey - 1962 New York - 1959-1962 New York Botanical Garden - 1961 (Box 40, Folder 452)
  - Nicaragua - Ensayo de Observaciones de Colecciones Maices - Blanco & Amarillos, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - Nicaragua - Ensayo Uniforme de Rendimiento, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 454)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 455)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 456)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 457)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 41, Folder 458)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 41, Folder 459)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 41, Folder 460)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 41, Folder 461)
  - Nicaragua - General Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 41, Folder 462)
  - Nicholson, Edward G., 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 463)
  - Niederhauser, John S. - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1963 (Box 41, Folder 464)
  - Niederhauser, John S. - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1963 (Box 41, Folder 465)
  - Niederhauser, John S. - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947-1963 (Box 41, Folder 466)
  - Niederhauser, John S. - Trip Diaries, 1949, 1953, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 467)
  - Niederhauser, John S. - Trip Diaries, 1949, 1953, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 468)
  - Nigeria - 1961-1962 Non-Scholarship Foreign Trainees - 1952-1955 Normas para la Siemba de Maiz en Tapalcingo - 1960-1961, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 469)
  - North Carolina State College - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 42, Folder 470)
  - North Carolina State College - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 42, Folder 471)
  - North Carolina State College - General Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 42, Folder 472)
  - Nuevo Leon, State of, 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 473)
  - Nutrition - 1949 Nutrition Cooperative Program - 1961 Nutritive Value of Corn Varieties - 1960, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 474)
  - Oaxaca, State of, 1952-1960 (Box 42, Folder 475)
  - O.E.E. (Oficina de Estudios Especiales) - Budgets, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 476)
  - O.E.E. - Commissioned Personnel - General Correspondence, 1945-1956 (Box 42, Folder 477)
  - O.E.E. - Commissioned Personnel - Miscellaneous Lists, 1945-1953 (Box 42, Folder 478)
  - O.E.E. - Commissioned Personnel - Payroll Lists, 1948-1955 (Box 43, Folder 479)
  - O.E.E. - Commissioned Personnel - Stipend Authorizations/Payroll Changes, 1956-1958 (Box 43, Folder 480)
  - O.E.E. Committees - 1956 Contratos de Trabajo - 1961, 1956-1961 (Box 43, Folder 481)
  - O.E.E. - Entomology Reports, 1945-1960 (Box 43, Folder 482)
  - O.E.E. - Equipment, 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 483)
  - O.E.E. - Expense Accounts, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 484)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Conference, April 30-May 2, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 485)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Demonstrations, 1948-1955 (Box 43, Folder 486)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Reports, 1949, 1954-1960 (Box 43, Folder 487)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Reports, 1949, 1954-1960 (Box 43, Folder 488)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Reports, 1949, 1954-1960 (Box 43, Folder 489)
  - O.E.E. - Extension Services - Reports, 1949, 1954-1960 (Box 43, Folder 490)
  - O.E.E. - Greenhouse (Chapingo), 1948 (Box 43, Folder 491)
  - O.E.E. History - 1959 Inter-Office Memoranda - 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 492)
  - O.E.E. - Inventory, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 493)
  - O.E.E. Junior Staff Officers - 1952-1955 Library - 1960, 1952-1960 (Box 44, Folder 494)
  - O.E.E. - Miscellaneous Office Files, 1954-1961 (Box 44, Folder 495)
  - O.E.E. - Miscellaneous Office Files, 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 496)
  - O.E.E. - Newsletter, 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 497)